click4college.com 2013-09-05

# Privacy Policy - click4college.com

**Click4College** is a user based site whose goal is to unite students with college success and opportunity. References in this Privacy Policy may, as the context requires, include Click4College.com, and any other subsidiaries or affiliates of Click4College (C4C). C4C provides access to information and services that ease the transition from high school to college which can make the college experience more enjoyable and cost friendly. We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy rights of our users. 

This Privacy Policy applies only to personally identifiable information collected on this website and does not apply to any other information collected by C4C through other avenues. This Privacy Policy applies to the use and sharing of personally identifiable information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 17. If a child provides us with this type of information online, please contact us to have the account deactivated by sending an email to [info@click4college.com](mailto:info@click4college.com).

Our world is constantly changing and as such, so does this Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may need to amend our Privacy Policy because of changes in the law, technology, our business, or our attempts to better serve user needs. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes within the Privacy Policy itself, on the homepage, or in other appropriate locales. Although changes are rare, it is your responsibility as the user to stay abreast of changes we have made and posted.

As a site that is designed to assist and aid you, the user, in the college process, it is completely up to you what information you disclose to us. If you choose not to provide necessary information, we may not be able to fully serve your needs but under no circumstances do we force information to be submitted. 

We respect and acknowledge your privacy. Except as described in this privacy statement, your information collected by C4C.com will not be shared or disseminated to any private third party.

In accordance with our law abiding stance on cyber crime, we do reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

College is not cheap, and in an attempt to ease that blow, we offer a variety of tools and services which provide access to current information on college costs. These include scholarship lists, financial aid assistance, education loan paperwork, and government agencies that might be able to help. We typically collect the following information when these tools are used: first and last name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, anticipated graduation date, family information, and social security number (optional). For more specific items like scholarships and financial aid forms, additional fields specific to the request might also be needed.

We pride ourselves in our secure transmission of information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Once we receive your information, we take all necessary precautions to ensure its security on our systems and do so by immediately encrypting the information stored. When sensitive information such as credit card or social security numbers are transmitted, we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

C4C may collect personal information and data including, but not limited to: email and personal contact information, IP Address and other identifiable information. C4C may use technological means for tagging and tracking data including, but not limited to, harmless cookies, clear .GIFs, and other technologies to track and correlate data. 

Personally identifiable information submitted by a User is used to provide features of the Website for the User's use and benefit. C4C uses clear .GIFs and log file data to: (i) provide custom content and preferences; (ii) monitor the impact and effectiveness of C4C marketing efforts; (iii) monitor aggregate metrics providing detailed data on User activities while on the Website; (iv) track your submissions, entries, and status. 

a. C4C provides information on Users to subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and third party vendors for the purpose of processing such information on behalf of C4C. At all times, these parties are required to agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, and we exercise reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information. 

b. C4C reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable and/or non-personally identifiable information that is believed, in good faith, to be appropriate or necessary for the purpose of enforcing the C4C Privacy Policy, or other governing C4C policies. Other causes of release of data may be due to, but not limited to: (i) taking precautions against liability issues; (ii) to assist government enforcement agencies; (iii) to investigate and defend C4C against third party claims or allegations; (iv) to protect the security or integrity of the Website and/or Services; and/or (v) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of C4C, Users of the Website, or others. 

c. C4C does share non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous User data and traffic data, with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns and trends analysis for certain content, advertisements, promotions, services, and/or functionality of the Website.
